Guide to the William C. Bullitt Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1882-1967; Series I
  The writing and publication of Thomas Woodrow Wilson as well as Sigmund Freud's emigration from Austria is discussed in the correspondence among Bullitt, Sigmund Freud, and Anna Freud. Other correspondence with Sigmund Freud, Anna Freud, and Ernst Freud about Thomas Woodrow Wilson can be found in Series II. Bullitt's work as a journalist is discussed in the correspondence with Henry R. Luce, Life Magazine, Time Inc., DeWitt Wallace, and Reader's Digest. A substantial amount of material concerns Bullitt's opposition to communism, especially in the late 1940s and 1950s, and can be found in the correspondence with Clarence K. Streit, Alfred Kohlberg, Douglas H. Allen, Laurence B. Keiser, Charles T. Mayer, Leopold Braun, Francis Spellman, Styles Bridges, E. W. Capen, William Henry Chamberlain, S. M. Levitas, Albert C. Wedemeyer, Upton Sinclair, Dwight D. Eisenhower, William F. Knowland, and Eugene Lyons. Bullitt's ties to Taiwan are represented in his correspondence with Chang Ming-kai, Pai Shiu Chuan, Sampson C. Shen, Pei Tsuyee, V. K. Wellington Koo, General Sun Li-jen, George Kungchao Yeh, Generalissimo and Madame Chiang Kai-shek, Konsin C. Shah, and Karl L. Rankin; to Korea, in his correspondence with Whang Ey Chan, Syngman Rhee; and to Vietnam, in his correspondence with Do Van Bong. His interests in a united Europe are documented in his correspondence with Richard N. Coudenhove-Kalergi. Bullitt also assisted a number of individuals in their immigration to the United States which is reflected in the correspondence of Stefan Osusky and Pai Shiu Chuan, among others.
  Bullitt's friendship with a number of prominent composers, artists, and writers is represented in the correspondence with Marsden Hartley, George Antheil, John Barber, George Biddle, Archibald MacLeish, Lincoln Steffens, William Carlos Williams, Upton Sinclair, Oswald Garrison Villard, Max Eastman, William Shirer, and Lincoln Colcord. For material on Bullitt's campaign for mayor of Philadelphia in 1943, see the files for Albert F. Ceres and James P. Clark.
  - A-An (Box 1, Folder 1 - 13)
  - Ap-Az (Box 2, Folder 14 - 18)
  - A. N. Marquis Company, 1933-1948 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Aaronsohn, Rifka, 1949-1955, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Acheson, Dean, 1933, 1941-1950 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Adlon, Louis, 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Albright, Edward, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Alexander, Jack, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Algase, Gertrude, 1938-1940, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Alkend, Leyla [includes photographs], 1936-1940, 1945-1955, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Allen, Douglas H., 1933-1937, 1942, 1949-1952 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Allez, Mary Paul, 1938-1940, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Allison, John M., 1952-1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Allstorm, Oliver, 1947
    General note
    See: Oversize Folder 35
  - Alphand, Charles, 1934-1940, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Alphand, Claude, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Altschul, Frank, 1939, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Ames, A. A., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - American Association of Teachers of French, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - American China Policy Association, Inc., 1947-1950 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    See also: Oversize Folder 1
    See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 1087 - 1091
  - The American Hospital of Paris, 1937-1945, 1952, 1964, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - The American Legion, 1941, 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The American Library in Paris, Inc., 1943-1949 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - The American Red Cross, 1942-1943, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Amlie, Milly, 1940-1952 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Andreytchine, George, 1933-1934, 1941-1942, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Antheil, George [includes photographs], 1924, 1933-1943, 1954, undated (Box 3, Folder 42 - 45)
  - Antheil, Henry W., Jr., 1934-1940, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Apponyi, Anton, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1933-1946 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Arnett, Elizabeth H., 1933, 1941-1943, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Armanet, V. Crescent, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Arnold, Marion [includes photographs], 1938-1940 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Ashfield, Massachusetts, Town of, 1936, 1952-1962 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Astor, Nancy, 1919, 1933-1959 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Astor, William Waldorf, Jr., 1936-1939, 1944-1951 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Astor, William Waldorf, III, 1933-1934, 1940, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Atherton, Ray, 1934-1942 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Aug. Michel [Company], 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Auriol, Vincent, 1938-1951 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Baa-Bel (Box 4, Folder 60 - 80)
  - Bem-Blu (Box 5, Folder 81 - 98)
  - Boa-Bry (Box 6, Folder 99 - 120)
  - Buc-Byr (Box 7, Folder 121 - 131)
  - Babb, James T., 1941-1960 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Bach, Charles T., 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Baer, Joseph, 1933-1940 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Baer, Lelia L., 1933-1943 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Baeyens, James and Mary Clark, 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Bagger, Eugene, 1926-1941 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Bailey, David Algar, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Bain, Steelman, 1933-1943 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Baker, Russell, 1952-1962 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Balderston, C. Canby, 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Baliozian, Couchane, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Baltrusiatis, Jurgis, 1937-1947 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Barber, Charles H., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Barber, John, 1934-1963 (Box 7, Folder 145 - 146)
  - Barkley, Alben and Dorothy, 1938-1941 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Barnes, Albert C., 1937-1950 (Box 8, Folder 148 - 149)
  - Barnes, Laura L., 1950-1958 (Box 8, Folder 150 - 151)
  - Barnes, Maynard B., 1938-1942 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Barney, Natalie Clifford, 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Barrett, Dave, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Bartholomew, Marshall, 1934-1946, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Barlett, Valentine C., 1940-1947 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Baruch, Bernard, 1933-1948 (Box 8, Folder 157 - 158)
  - Bastianello, Raymond, 1939-1941 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Bate, Fred, 1938-1941 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Bates-Batcheller, Tryphosa, 1938-1947 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Battles, H. H., 1932-1941 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Bauer, J. M., 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Beekman, Frederick W. and Margaret, 1937-1948 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Bell, Ulric, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Bement, Lewis D., 1933-1951 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Bement School, 1933-1947, undated (Box 8, Folder 167 - 169)
  - Ben-Horin, Eliahu, 1944-1949 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Benzoni, Maria, 1937-1941, 1946-1953 (Box 8, Folder 171 - 172)
  - Bérard, E., 1939 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Berardis, Vicenzo, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Bergman, Alfred, 1937-1939 (Box 9, Folder 175 - 176)
  - Bernstein, Henry, 1939-1943 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Berry, Frank B., 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Berton, S. R., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Bess, Demaree, 1940-1954 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Biddle, Anthony J. Drexel, Jr., 1934-1951, undated (Box 9, Folder 181 - 185)
  - Biddle, Francis, 1930-1944 (Box 9, Folder 186 - 187)
  - Biddle, George [includes photographs], 1924-1966, undated (Box 9, Folder 188 - 189)
  - Biddle, Margaret T., 1937-1952, undated (Box 9, Folder 190 - 193)
  - Biddle, Nicholas, Jr., 1941-1961, undated (Box 10, Folder 194)
  - Billings, Arthur Goodwin, 1940-1952 (Box 10, Folder 195)
  - Billings, Josh S., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - Bird, Sally and William, 1933-1942 (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - Bizard, Jean, 1939-1948 (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - Blackburn, Katherine C., 1933-1943 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Blake, Maurice, 1908-1915, 1933-1939, undated (Box 10, Folder 200)
  - Bland, Elizabeth N., 1941-1948, undated (Box 10, Folder 201)
  - Bliss, Mildred, 1939-1949 (Box 10, Folder 202)
  - Blum, Leon, 1923, 1938-1951, undated (Box 10, Folder 203)
  - Blum, Suzanne [Mrs. Paul Weill], 1938-1957, undated (Box 10, Folder 204 - 206)
  - Bohlen, Avis, 1939-1943, undated (Box 10, Folder 207)
  - Bohlen, Charles E., 1939, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 208)
  - Bonnet, Georges, 1936-1940 (Box 10, Folder 209)
  - Borie, C. Louis, 1934-1943 (Box 10, Folder 210)
  - Borie, Edith, 1933-1946, undated (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - Boris, Georges, 1937-1942 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - Bosworth, Welles, 1938-1952 (Box 10, Folder 213)
  - Bove, Charles F., 1940-1942 (Box 10, Folder 214)
  - Bowers, Claude G., 1937-1939 (Box 10, Folder 215)
  - Boyer, Maurice, 1938-1942 (Box 10, Folder 216)
  - Boyer, Paul, 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - Brady, Thomas, 1919, 1933-1942 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Braun, Leopold [includes photographs], 1934-1960, undated (Box 10, Folder 220 - 223)
  - Bridges, Styles, 1947-1961 (Box 11, Folder 224)
  - Briggs, Doloris and Ellis O., 1951-1962 (Box 11, Folder 225)
  - Brougham, Herbert Bruce, 1917-1940 (Box 11, Folder 226)
  - Browder, Robert P., 1949-1952 (Box 11, Folder 227)
  - Brown, Coleman P., 1933-1956 (Box 11, Folder 228)
  - Brown, Lestrade, 1938-1942 (Box 11, Folder 229)
  - Bruyère, Paul, 1941-1942 (Box 11, Folder 230)
  - Bryant, Louise [includes photographs], 1921-1934, undated (Box 11, Folder 231 - 242)
  - Buckler, William H., 1919, 1940-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 243)
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 244)
  - Budd, Ralph J., 1942, undated (Box 12, Folder 245)
  - Buell, Raymond Leslie, 1934-1940 (Box 12, Folder 246)
  - Bullitt, Aimée Ernesta Drinker, 1912-1922, 1940-1941, undated (Box 12, Folder 247 - 255)
  - Bullitt, Anne Moen [includes photographs], 1929-1937 (Box 12, Folder 256 - 259)
  - Bullitt, Anne Moen [includes photographs], 1938-1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 260 - 281)
  - Bullitt, Dorothy R., 1940-1944 (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - Bullitt, Dorothy S., 1937-1948, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Bullitt, James B., 1937-1952 (Box 14, Folder 284)
  - Bullitt, James Fry and Margaret, 1933-1954, undated (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - Bullitt, John C., 1933-1949, undated (Box 14, Folder 286)
  - Bullitt, Logan, 1933-1941 (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - Bullitt, Louisa, 1936-1947, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 288)
  - Bullitt, Louisa H., 1882, 1908-1916, undated (Box 14, Folder 289 - 295)
  - Bullitt, Nora, 1933-1956, undated (Box 14, Folder 296 - 298)
  - Bullitt, Orville H., 1911-1939 (Box 14, Folder 299 - 306)
  - Bullitt, Orville H., 1940-1966, undated (Box 15, Folder 307 - 315)
  - Bullitt, Orville H., Jr., 1937-1946 (Box 15, Folder 316)
  - Bullitt, Rita, 1933-1943, undated (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Bullitt, Stimson [includes photographs], 1942-1948 (Box 15, Folder 318)
  - Bullitt, Susan B., 1933-1966 (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Bullitt, Thomas W., 1935-1962 (Box 15, Folder 320 - 323)
  - Bullitt, William C., Sr., 1886, 1908-1911, [ca 1956] (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Bullitt, William Marshall, 1917-1942 (Box 15, Folder 325 - 332)
  - Bullitt, William Marshall [includes photographs], 1943-1957, undated (Box 16, Folder 333 - 337)
  - Bumgardner, Eleanor, 1950-1957 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Bunau-Varilla, Philippe, 1933-1939, undated (Box 16, Folder 339 - 340)
  - Bunn, Edward B., 1953-1963, undated (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Burkinshaw, Neil, 1920-1943 (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Burlingham, Dorothy, 1933-1940 (Box 16, Folder 343)
  - Bussod, André, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - Byington, Homer, 1940-1943 (Box 16, Folder 345)
  - Byrnes, James F., 1935-1948 (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - C-Carv (Box 16, Folder 347 - 354)
  - Cas-Clu (Box 17, Folder 355 - 371)
  - Coa-Cut (Box 18, Folder 372 - 390)
  - Cabanes, Pierre, 1939-1947 (Box 19, Folder 391)
  - Cachin, Marcel, 1936-1938 (Box 19, Folder 392)
  - Cadwalader, Mae, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 393)
  - Callaghan and Shaw, 1938-1950, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 394)
  - Capen, E. W., 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 395)
  - Carleton, Don E., 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 396)
  - Carney, Robert B., 1953-1961 (Box 19, Folder 397)
  - Carroll, Vincent A., 1943 (Box 19, Folder 398)
  - Carriger, William C., 1963-1965, undated (Box 19, Folder 399)
  - Ceres, Albert F. "Scoop", Jr., 1933-1944, 1959, undated (Box 19, Folder 400 - 401)
  - Chamberlain,William Henry, 1933, 1943-1950 (Box 19, Folder 402)
  - Chang Ming-kai [includes photographs], 1954-1963, undated (Box 19, Folder 403 - 404)
  - Chappell, Carol, 1933-1939 (Box 19, Folder 405)
  - Chappell, Frank Valentine, 1933-1955 (Box 19, Folder 406)
  - Charles Chalk Company, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 407)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons Publishers, 1946-1954 (Box 19, Folder 408)
  - Chattin, Frederick W., 1912-1915 (Box 19, Folder 409)
  - Chautemps, Camille, 1936-1946 (Box 19, Folder 410)
  - Cheatam, Kitty, 1933-1934, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 411)
  - Chen Chih-mai, 1948-1954 (Box 19, Folder 412)
  - Chen Pin-ho, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 413)
  - Chew, Oswald, 1937-1943 (Box 19, Folder 414)
    See also: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 668
  - Chiang Ching-kuo, 1955-1956, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 415)
  - Chiang, Franklin C., 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 416)
  - Chiang Kai-shek, 1940, 1942, 1945-1953, 1956, undated (Box 19, Folder 417)
    See also: Series II. Diplomatic and Public Service Papers, 1813-1956 Folder 414
  - Chiang, Mayling Soong [Madame Chiang Kai-shek], 1934-1947, 1954-1955, undated (Box 19, Folder 418)
  - Ching, Peter P. S., 1950-1954, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 419)
  - Chipman, Fanny S., 1940-1942 (Box 19, Folder 420)
  - Chipman, Norris B., 1939-1955 (Box 19, Folder 421)
  - The Christianform, 1950-1952 (Box 20, Folder 422)
  - Churchill, Winston, 1942-1951 (Box 20, Folder 423)
  - Clarac, Claude Achille-Marie, 1933-1938, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 424)
  - Clark, Charles Upson, 1933, 1939-1941 (Box 20, Folder 425)
  - Clark, Grenville, 1941, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - Clark H. Getts, Inc., 1940, 1946-1952 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Clark, James P., 1942-1944 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Clark, Lewis, 1937-1941, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Claudel, Paul, 1933-1938 (Box 20, Folder 430)
  - Clayton, William L., 1940-1965 (Box 20, Folder 431)
  - Clemens, Cyril, 1944-1952 (Box 20, Folder 432)
  - Clews, Marie Elsie, 1938-1946, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Close, Edward B., 1938-1942 (Box 20, Folder 434)
  - Clothier, Anita Porter, 1940, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 435)
  - Coe, Caroline, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 436)
  - Cogswell, Francis and Grace, 1939-1943, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 437)
  - Colcord, Lincoln, 1917-1920, 1927-1938 (Box 20, Folder 438 - 439)
  - Cole, Felix, 1936-1940 (Box 20, Folder 440)
  - Coleman, Marianna "Babs", 1937-1943 (Box 20, Folder 441)
  - Colgate University, 1949-1952 (Box 20, Folder 442)
  - Collins, Alan C., 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 443)
  - Colloredo-Mansfeld, Ferdinand, 1933-1937, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 444)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS), 1939-1943, 1948-1949, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 445)
  - Comert, Pierre, 1932-1939 (Box 20, Folder 446)
  - Compagnie Générale Transatlantique, 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 447)
  - Cone, J. Carroll, 1940-1943 (Box 20, Folder 448)
  - Confrérie des Chevaliers du Tastevin [includes photographs], 1937-1948 (Box 21, Folder 449 - 450)
  - Cooke, Charles M., 1948-1954 (Box 21, Folder 451)
  - Cooke, Morris L., 1917, 1920, 1934, 1943, 1953, 1955, undated (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Cornwall, Laurence M., 1939-1942, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 453)
  - Cortwright, Nareit[?], 1963-1967 (Box 21, Folder 454)
  - Cotnareanu, Leon, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 455)
  - Coudenhove-Kalergi, Richard N., 1933-1958, undated (Box 21, Folder 456 - 459)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Council on Foreign Relations [includes photographs], 1938-1949 (Box 21, Folder 461)
  - Cowles, Gardner "Mike", 1950-1954 (Box 21, Folder 462)
  - Crane, John O., 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 463)
  - Crichton, Andrew B., 1940-1943 (Box 21, Folder 464)
  - Crichton, Kyle, 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 465)
  - Croly, Herbert, 1918-1920, undated (Box 21, Folder 466)
  - Cromwell, William Nelson, 1936-1941 (Box 21, Folder 467 - 468)
  - Crowninshield, Frank, 1934, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 469)
  - Cudahy, John, 1933-1942, undated (Box 22, Folder 470 - 475)
  - Cudahy, Katherine R., 1947-1949 (Box 22, Folder 476)
  - Cunningham, Harry F., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 477)
  - Curtis Brown, Ltd.
    See: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 443
  - Curtiss, Mina, 1933-1943 (Box 22, Folder 478)
  - Cutting, Helen [includes photographs], 1939-1946 (Box 22, Folder 479)
  - Cuttoli, Marie, 1937-1954, undated (Box 22, Folder 480 - 481)
  - Dab-Dem (Box 22, Folder 482 - 489)
  - Den-Dz (Box 23, Folder 490 - 504)
  - Daguet, Jacques, 1946-1949 (Box 24, Folder 505)
  - Daladier, Edouard, 1938- 1954 (Box 24, Folder 506)
  - Daladier, Jean, 1939-1953 (Box 24, Folder 507)
  - Dallin, David J., 1941-1955 (Box 24, Folder 508)
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1934-1941 (Box 24, Folder 509)
  - D'Argent, Marquise, 1936-1940, undated (Box 24, Folder 510)
  - Dartmouth College, 1939-1941, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 511)
  - D'Assergio, Alice, 1916, 1929-1941, undated (Box 24, Folder 512)
  - Davenport, Marion Keith, 1937-1940, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 513)
  - Davies, Joseph E., 1936-1943 (Box 24, Folder 514 - 515)
  - Davies, Marjorie, 1937-1942 (Box 24, Folder 516)
  - Davis, Jerome, 1933-1935 (Box 24, Folder 517)
  - Day, Frederic, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 518)
  - Day, George Parmly, 1916, 1933-1938, 1945-1956 (Box 24, Folder 519)
  - Deacon & Allen, 1933, undated (Box 24, Folder 520)
  - Dean, Michael M. "Sabahattin" [includes photographs], 1934- 1967, undated (Box 24, Folder 521)
  - De Bellaigue, P., 1942-1951 (Box 24, Folder 522)
  - De Bénouville, Guillain, 1947-1952 (Box 24, Folder 523)
  - De Chambrun, René, 1938-1948 (Box 24, Folder 524)
  - De Curtis, Domenico, 1942-1962 (Box 24, Folder 525)
  - Deegan, Elizabeth, 1940-1946 (Box 24, Folder 526)
  - De Gaulle, Charles, 1944-1945, 1954, 1961, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 527)
  - De Hedervary, Khuen and Klari, 1941, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 528)
  - De Lamaziere, R. Calary [includes photographs], 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 529)
  - Delano, William Adams, 1937-1941, 1947-1951 (Box 24, Folder 530)
  - De Lanux, Eyre and Pierre, 1933-1941 (Box 24, Folder 531)
  - De Lattre De Tassigny, Jean, 1943-1955, undated (Box 24, Folder 532)
  - Del Sarte, Maxime Real [includes photographs], 1939 (Box 25, Folder 533)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1939-1944 (Box 25, Folder 534)
  - Democrats for Dewey, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 535)
  - De Polignac, Melchior, 1936-1939 (Box 25, Folder 536)
  - De Polignac, Nina Crosby, 1934-1939 (Box 25, Folder 537)
  - De Portes, Countess, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 538)
  - De Rochechouart, Countess, 1938 (Box 25, Folder 539)
  - De Sales, Raoul De Roussy, 1938-1942, undated (Box 25, Folder 540)
  - De Schaub, Ella, 1940-1942 (Box 25, Folder 541)
  - De Sonis, Countess, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 542)
  - De Valéra, Eamon, 1938-1957 (Box 25, Folder 543)
  - Dewey, Charles S., 1939-1941, 1948-1949 (Box 25, Folder 544)
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1947-1953 (Box 25, Folder 545)
  - Dick, Langhorne B., 1934-1940 (Box 25, Folder 546)
  - Dickinson, Jacob McGavock, 1933-1934, 1941, 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 547)
  - Didier, J. P., 1940-1948 (Box 25, Folder 548)
  - Dill, Dwight, 1953-1966 (Box 25, Folder 549)
  - Dillingham, Walter F., 1948-1959 (Box 25, Folder 550)
  - Disston, William D., 1933-1934 (Box 25, Folder 551)
  - District of Columbia, Government of the, 1934, 1941- 1946, 1953, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 552)
  - Do Van Bong, 1945-1965 (Box 25, Folder 553 - 554)
  - Dodd, William E., 1934-1938 (Box 25, Folder 555)
  - Donovan, William, 1941-1943, 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 556)
  - Doolittle, Lytton, 1933, 1938-1946 (Box 25, Folder 557)
  - Dorel, G., 1928-1958, undated (Box 25, Folder 558)
  - Douglas, Lewis W., 1933-1935, 1940-1942 (Box 25, Folder 559)
  - Douglas, Richard A., 1913, 1919, 1933-1935, 1941 (Box 25, Folder 560)
  - Downe, Ethel, 1938-1951, 1958, undated (Box 25, Folder 561 - 562)
    See also: Oversize Folder 85
  - Doyle, Michael Francis, 1938, 1943-1944, undated (Box 25, Folder 563)
  - Draper, Muriel, 1933-1934 (Box 26, Folder 564)
  - Drexel, Constance, 1933, 1939, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 565)
  - Drinker, Ernesta
    See: Series I. Correspondence, 1882-1967 Folder 247 - 255
  - Drück, Gertrud, 1938-1939, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 566)
  - Duggan, Stephen, 1933-1935, 1943 (Box 26, Folder 567)
  - Dulles, Allen W., 1919, 1933-1934, 1947-1953 (Box 26, Folder 568)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1939-1955 (Box 26, Folder 569)
  - Dunn, James Clement, 1933, 1937-1952 (Box 26, Folder 570)
  - Dupasquier, Pierre, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 571)
  - Durbrow, Emily, 1938, 1946-1948 (Box 26, Folder 572)
  - Dustin, Alfred, 1946-1950 (Box 26, Folder 573)
  - DuVal, Lucy, 1940-1942 (Box 26, Folder 574)
  - E (Box 26, Folder 575 - 581)
  - Earle, George H., 1933-1953 (Box 26, Folder 582 - 583)
  - Earle, Huberta P., 1933-1944, 1946 (Box 27, Folder 584 - 585)
  - Early, Stephen T., 1933-1938, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 586)
  - Eastman, Max, 1920, 1933-1936, 1943, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 587)
  - Ebon, Martin and Mary, 1940-1948 (Box 27, Folder 588)
  - Edelman, Samuel, 1934-1941 (Box 27, Folder 589)
  - Edgar, Joseph S., 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 590)
  - Edinger, Marietta, 1940-1944 (Box 27, Folder 591)
  - Edison, Charles, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 592)
  - Ehmke, Lester D., 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 593)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1940-1941 (Box 27, Folder 594)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1946, 1953-1955 (Box 27, Folder 595)
  - Eklund, Ernest I., 1933-1934 (Box 27, Folder 596)
  - Elkins, Sheble, and Company [includes photographs], 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 597 - 598)
  - Elliot, George E., 1933-1934 (Box 27, Folder 599)
  - Elliot, Zo, 1933-1943 (Box 27, Folder 600)
  - Ely, Gertrude, 1934-1950 (Box 27, Folder 601)
  - Ely, Robert Erskins, 1936, 1939-1944 (Box 27, Folder 602)
  - Emmons, George W., 1941-1942 (Box 27, Folder 603)
  - Engard, Charles I., 1940-1942 (Box 27, Folder 604)
  - The English Speaking Union, 1942-1947, undated (Box 27, Folder 605)
  - Epworth, Lincoln, 1949 (Box 27, Folder 606)
  - Eriksson-Hyyrylainen, Elli [includes photographs], 1948-1950 (Box 27, Folder 607)
  - Ervin, Charles W., 1936, 1942-1943 (Box 27, Folder 608)
  - Esmond, Edward, 1938-1944 (Box 27, Folder 609)
  - Estes, Charles T., 1940 (Box 27, Folder 610)
  - Evans, Allen, 1940-1947, undated (Box 27, Folder 611)
  - Evans, Ernestine, 1919, 1933-1943 (Box 27, Folder 612)
  - Evans, Rowland, 1933, 1940-1946, 1950-1962 (Box 27, Folder 613)
  - Everitt, John Thompson, [ca 1941] (Box 27, Folder 614)
  - Ewell, R. Douglas, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 615)
  - Excoffier, Louis, 1937-1939 (Box 27, Folder 616)
  - Exton, Frederick, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 617)
  - F-Fra (Box 28, Folder 618 - 632)
  - Fre-Fu (Box 29, Folder 633 - 635)
  - Farley, James A., 1933-1946, 1949-1962, undated (Box 29, Folder 636 - 646)
  - Fay, Bernard, 1936-1939 (Box 29, Folder 647)
  - Federal Union, 1941-1948 (Box 29, Folder 648)
  - Feis, Herbert, 1934-1943, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 649)
  - Ferguson, Homer and Myrtle, 1947-1952 (Box 29, Folder 650)
  - Filar, Maryan, 1950-1957, 1961, undated (Box 29, Folder 651)
  - Filene, Edward A., 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 652)
  - Filene, Lincoln, 1935-1937, undated (Box 29, Folder 653)
  - Flagg, William F., 1922, 1933-1934, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 654)
  - Flanner, Janet, 1938-1941 (Box 30, Folder 655)
  - Fleck, Charles E., 1938-1940, 1946-1953, undated (Box 30, Folder 656)
  - Flipo, Pierre, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 657)
  - Focillon, Marguerite H. and Henri, 1940-1943, undated (Box 30, Folder 658 - 660)
  - Foerster, F. W., 1939-1942 (Box 30, Folder 661)
  - Fong, Lloyd S. C., 1948-1951 (Box 30, Folder 662)
  - Ford, John Howard, 1943-1946 (Box 30, Folder 663)
  - Forrestal, James, 1940-1948, undated (Box 30, Folder 664)
  - Forrestal, Michael, 1948-1950 (Box 30, Folder 665)